We're excited to have you here in the
Carolinas.
>> I can't wait. I'm so excited, too.
>> All right, we'll kick things off. Any
questions, guys?
>> Hey, Jackson. Mike K from the Charlotte
Observer. Congratulations.
>> Thank you. I appreciate
>> how you pronounce your last name.
>> It's Kwatch.
>> Kwatch. Okay. So,
>> um obviously transferring from Ohio
State, it took kind of a while to get
going in Miami. Um
>> how how did the light switch kind of
turn on? whether it was the opportunity
or just your style of play that final
year at Miami.
>> Yeah, I think uh you know I think a big
part of that was the opportunity um and
you know my mindset. Um, I feel like I
had a, you know, a switch in mindset and
I kind of just went out there and
played. Um, and I think I did a good job
of, you know, learning from, uh,
learning from mistakes and, you know,
you know, film junkie and, um, so yeah,
I think it was a it was a mindset and
kind of just letting loose and playing
ball really.
>> Uh, the Panthers were all out in full
force, the Shrine Bowl, uh, after you
got the the call up from the Hoola Bowl.
Yeah. Um
>> how do you feel like you established
yourself there? Why was that an
important opportunity for you?
>> Yeah, that was uh that was great
exposure for me. Um you know, being a
MAC player um going to Miami, Ohio. I
think uh that week at the Shrine Bowl
was super important for uh for me
throughout this pre-draft process to uh
you know, kind of prove and uh prove to
people that I belonged and you know,
that I compete that I could compete with
you know, some of the best uh talent out
there. So I think it was a, you know,
very important week for me.
>> And then the Panthers say they ask about
the why of a player, why they played
football. What was your answer to that?
>> Yeah, my why football is everything I've
known from, you know, I started playing
in second grade. um you know was the
first true you know love of my life and
you know it it hasn't stopped being um
you know I have so much fun playing the
game and I you know my real answer for
that is sorry I'm getting calls my real
answer for that would be uh hold on my
bad I'm getting my phone's getting calls
I would say that you know that feeling
of that first you know that first hit in
the game that adrenaline rush like
there's nothing like it. Um, you know,
you get a little nerves and a little
anxious before games and, you know, just
go out there and able to hit somebody.
>> So, how important is special teams to
you that opening kickoff?
>> Extremely important. Yeah, I've played
uh I don't know what the exact number
is, but I think close to 450 career
snaps on special teams. I've always been
a big contributor in my college career
and, you know, look to do the same at
the next level for the Panthers.
Cass
Hi, Jackson. Congratulations.
>> Hi, thank you. A
>> a linebacker from Cincinnati. I feel
like I have to ask, how much did you
grow up watching Luke Keegel?
>> I grew up watching him a lot. He was
actually uh he was my favorite player.
Probably still is my favorite player
ever. Um so yeah, grew up watching him a
lot.
>> Have you ever got to meet him before?
>> I have not. I have not.
>> I think we could probably arrange that
now.
>> Yeah, that would be surreal. That would
be awesome.
And then you had five sacks this past
year. What is the key to being a
blitzing linebacker?
>> Yeah, I think it's just your intent when
you blitz. Um, you know, the aggressive
nature of blitzing and um, you know, I
think I'm a twitchy pushy player and,
you know, quick players. So, I think
that helps me out when I'm blitzing,
too. But really just your mindset and
intent when blitzing, I would say.
>> Thank you.
>> Yeah, of course.
>> Any more questions for Jackson?
Uh yeah, I just Hi, I've asked Shai. I
can't put on my camera. I apologize. But
if you could just describe your style of
play for fans who who might not be
familiar with your game.
>> Yeah. Yeah. My style of play I would
describe as um as twitchy, quick. Um
feel like I'm a sideline to sideline
linebacker. Um, I am a, you know, a
bigger bigger person, a taller person,
but, you know, I feel like I play the
game, uh, low, you know, tackle low and,
um, got some flexibility in my legs. So,
yeah, that's how I would describe it.
>> What have the last few days been like
for you just waiting to hear your name
called and then just describe the moment
when you got the call from Dan Morgan
and the Carolina Panthers?
>> Yeah. Yeah, the last the last three days
have been crazy. um you know
specifically today just the the unknown
um of what was going to happen and uh so
yeah it was you know a little bit of a a
long day to start and then you know when
I got that call it was yeah you know was
to be honest with you it's pretty hard
to believe like it was a very surreal
moment you know I've been working um
since I was nine years old to achieve
this and uh it's it really is a dream
come true for me so it was it was very
surreal
Thanks and congratulations.
>> Thank you.
>> All right, Jackson, that seems to be all
the questions we have for you this
afternoon. Thanks for taking the time.
>> Of course. I appreciate you guys
>> and congratulations once again. We can't
wait to have you.
>> Thank you. Can't wait.